Finding aid for the Robert A. Kennard Papers LSC.2351
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Kennard Design Group projects, 1957-2015
  - Subseries 2.1: Los Angeles County, 1957-2003
    - Watts Illustrative Plans: Watts Urban Redevelopment Project No. 1, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Watts Urban Redevelopment Project No. 1, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Crenshaw Probation Building (338), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Greater Richmond Community Development Center (350), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
    - H Street Urban Renewal (357), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles High School (362), 1972 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Carson City Hall (384), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    - Scott United Methodist Church (403), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Northwest Recreation Center Publicity (405), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Northwest Recreation Center (405), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Golden State Mutual Life (406), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Impact Report: Pasadena (407), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Southern California Rapid Transit District: Environmental Analysis and System Recommendations, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Downtown Santa Ana Development Plan (416), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Long Beach AIP Award Story (435), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Rockwell International (438), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Carson Community Center (443), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Carson History (443), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Bank of America (454), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - LA Community College District - Mission College Feasibility Study (467), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4-6)
    - LA Community College District Land Use Feasibility Study Presentation to the Board (467), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - LA Mission College: Educational Program and Facilities Plan (467), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Permanent Campus for LA Mission College: Report to Board of Trustees (467), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Wilshire Corridor - Urban Design Study (475), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Hidden Trails (505), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Site Feasibility Study & Master Plan: Mission College, Los Angeles, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Van Nuys State Office Building (507), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
    - Bunker Hill Competition (526), 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Charles R. Drew University of Medicine and Science Master Plan (534), 1980 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Charles R. Drew Postgrad Medical School, Long Range Development Plan (535), 1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Drew Postgraduate Medical School - Financial Analysis of Land Acquisition Program (535), 1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Charles R. Drew Postgrad Medical School Program Brochures (536.1), 1980 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Department of Water and Power (DWP) Water Filtration Plant (541), 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Parkview Plaza (551), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Weingart Urban Center (552), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Weingart Urban, Los Angeles (552), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles International Airport (LAX) Heliport and Parking Structures 1, 3, and 4 (557), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles International Airport Parking Structure P3 P4 (557), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Skid Row Development Corporation (Div. Corp) (561), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Skid Row Redevelopment Corporation (561.1), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - La Brea Place (564), 1982 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Southern California Rapid Transit District: Basis for Design (565), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Southern California Rapid Transit District (SC RTD) Division 5 (565), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Metro Rail Project: Contract Unit Descriptions (574), 1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Boelter Hall (582), 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 4-6)
    - UCLA Retrofit School of Engineering and Applied Science (SEAS) - Engineering Unit IV (582), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7, Box 29, Folder 1)
    - UCLA Retrofit Boelter Hall (582), 1984 (Box 29, Folder 2-5)
    - Engineering I, UCLA (582), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Wright Ed Building, George Washington Prep High School (586), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - George Washington High School (586.1), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - George Washington High School Reconstruction Part 2 (586), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Long Beach Railroad (590), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Cal State Pomona Music Building (591), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Police 77th Street (597), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
    - UCLA Student Activities Center, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Central Library Renovations (600), 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Summit Ridge Park (602), 1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Department of Airports - Maintenance Office - Purchasing Warehouse (609), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 3, Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Silverlake Recreational Center, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Jefferson Senior High School (625), 1988 (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
    - King/Drew County Trauma Center (637), 1989 (Box 32, Folder 7, Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Martin Luther King (MLK) Pediatrics Child Care Center (637), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
    - Roybal Gerontology (644), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Van Nuys General Mail Facility (651), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cal State University Los Angeles (CSULA) Bio-Science Lab (656), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Fire Station No. 16, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Van Dorn District of Columbia (D.C.) Metro Station (662), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Housing Authority of the City of Los Angeles (HACLA) Office (665), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - University Club California State University Los Angeles (CSULA) (685), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Cox Housing (686), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Hollywood Bowl Renovation (689), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
    - Baldwin Hills Recreation Center (690), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Union Station Baggage Handling Facility, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
    - Chaiken Residence 704 (Alaska), 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Drew University Master Plan (Los Angeles), 1995 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Castaic Sports (Los Angeles), undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Sherman Oaks Branch Library (Los Angeles), 2003 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Photograph Catalog, 1979-1983 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - KDG Offices 60s-70s, 1960s-1970s (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Tamarind Apartments, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Zeiger Residence, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Ty Lin Office, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Hidden Trails, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Kennard Residence, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - First Unitarian Church - Hugh Handyman Center (CTR), 1960 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Kingsley Apartments, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Wilco Plumbing Co., 1961 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Culver City Unified School District, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Fenmore Residence, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Fulton Apartments, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Temple Akiba (Includes Older Synagogue), 1962 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Mardyman Residence, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Wil-Den Productions (Nancy Wilson's House), 1964 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Congregation Emanuel, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Temple Soleal, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Hyde Park School, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Elderly Housing - Southside, LA, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Watts Enterprises Plant, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Various Los Angeles Schools Projects Correspondences, 1960s-1970s (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Correspondences from Los Angeles Unified School District (LAUSD) Re:In-School Visits, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Transit-Based Housing Symposium: Case studies of 3 Metro stations, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - LA Eastside Corridor: Alternative Analysis/Environmental Impact Statement, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - LA City Artmobile, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Metro Red Line Main Yard and Shop Facility, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Wilshire/Normandie Station, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - First African Methodist Episcopal (FAME) Education Center (677), 1992 (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
    - New FAME Education Center Cecil L. Murray (677), 1992 (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
    - FAME Education Center (677), 1992 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2.2: Non-Los Angeles County Southern California, 1970-1988
    This subseries contains KDG projects that were completed outside of Los Angeles, but are still in Southern California including those in Riverside County and the surrounding areas.
    - San Fernando Valley Child Guidance Facility (396/364), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Long Beach Poly High (370), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Third College University of California, San Diego (UCSD) Part 1 (378/379), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - UCSD Third College (Part 2), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Placentia Main Post Office (397), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - San Luis Obispo General Plan and Regulatory System - Phase 1 Draft Report (418), 1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - San Luis Obispo Phase 2 Preliminary General Plan Report (418), 1974 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Bixby Ranch: Environmental Impact Report (442), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Valley View Property: Cost/Revenue and School Impact Analysis (442), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Los Alamitos Airbase (447), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Los Alamitos Housing Element (447), 1975 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Valley-South Waterman Community Development Plan No. 1 (453), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Valley-South Waterman Community Development Plan (453), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - UC San Diego (462), 1976 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Dana Point Photos (477), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Dana Point Tract 10086, Parcel 3 (477), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Huntington Beach Racquet Club (478), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Jerry L. Pettis Memorial Veterans Medical Center (558), 1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Missile Crew Training Facility (585), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Poway Dodge (618), 1988 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Santa Ana Redevelopment, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - University of California, Irvine (UCI) - Long Range Development Plan, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.3: Northern California, 1968-2015
    This subseries contains KDG projects that were completed or proposed in Northern California, including in San Francisco.
    - Prince Hall Apartments (293), 1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - More Oakland Residential Housing (MORH), West Oakland (307A), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Oak Center Neighborhood Center (320), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Taylor Memorial Housing (321), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Berkeley Way/Grove Apartments (346), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Hunter's Point - Top of the Hill (347), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Oak Center Towers Part 1 (358), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Oak Center Apartments Part 2 (358), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Compton Central Business Apartment (374), 1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Compton Rosecrans Development Project (375), 1972 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Oakland Middle School Publicity (385), 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Marcus Foster School Demolition (385), 1973/2015 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Marcus Foster Middle School, Oakland, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - US Post Office, Oakland Airports Station Concept (434), 1975 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Aerojet Investments Limited: San Ramon Facility, Fostoria Way (440), 1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - City of Pleasant Hill: Neighborhood Conservation Program Report 1: Survey and Analysis of Housing Needs (473), 1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Oakland Post Office, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2.4: Other US locations, 1970s-1980s
    While the majority of KDG's work was within Southern California, there were some projects that were done out-of-state which are documented within this subseries.
    - 14th Street Development - Redevelopment Land Agency - District of Columbia (388), 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Tuskegee Institute, Alabama (390), 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Braddock Road Station, Washington DC (399), 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) Tracon, Long Island, NY (420), 1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - FAA Tracon Draft Environmental Impact Statement (420), 1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - FAA Tracon Air Traffic Control, NY (420), 1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Atlanta Rapid Transit Authority (MARTA) - Atlanta, Georgia, 1970s-1980s (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2.5: International, 1970s-1983
    KDG did a few projects in other countries and territories, including Mexico and Puerto Rico. Those projects are documented in this subseries.
    - Surbana (429), 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Project Overview: Golf de Vallarta (445) (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Golf de Vallarta (445), 1976 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Condessa Vallarta (488), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Club Residencial "Los Tules" (491), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Los Tules, Puerto Rico (470), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Cancun Nautico/Cancun Fonatur, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Concept: Zanu (PF) Headquarters, Zimbabwe, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Zanu Patriotic Front (ZPF) Headquarters, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Cancun Nautico/Cancun Fornatur Part 1, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Africa Documents, 1960s-1970s (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2.6: Color slides, microfilm, and negatives, 1960s-1995
    This subseries contains slides, microfilm, and negatives that depict various KDG projects.
    - Boulevard Theatre (276), 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Prince Hall Apartments (293), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - 102nd Street School (294), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Fire Station #33 (301), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Central City Community Mental Health Center (302), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Hunter's Point (304), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Bank of America - Watts (305), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - MOHR Oakland Residential Housing Inc (307), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - MOHR Oakland Residential Housing Inc (307B), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Neighborhood Center (310), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Watts Renewal Plan (311), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Vine City (312), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Hunter's Point Child Care Center (313), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Center for Civil Initiative Inc (315), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - St Mark's Lutheran Church (316), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Hoover Elderly Housing, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Taylor Memorial Housing, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - MORH (Acorn) Commercial Center, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - St James Lutheran Church, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Inglewood Corp, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - 332 Watts Meeting Company, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Taylor Memorial Church, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - The Palisades - Lutheran Church, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Barr Res, Hidden Trails, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Greater Richmond Community Development Corp., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Marin City, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Washington H Street Urban Renewal, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - West Oakland Apartments, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Richmond Childcare Center, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Los Angeles High School, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - United States Post Office, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Long Beach Poly High NDP, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Compton CBD, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - UCSD Third College, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - UCSD Third College, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - North Inglewood Planning Study (381), 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Carson Civic Center (383), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Carson City Hall (384), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Oakland Middle School (385), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - 14th Street Corridor (388), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Kaiser Watts Learning Center (391), 1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) Braddock Road Station (399), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Scott United Methodist Church (403), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Northwest Recreation Center (405), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Golden State Mutual (406), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Pasadena Environmental Impact Study (EIR) Impact Study (407), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Cypress Housing Study - Wilsey and Ham (411), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Roosevelt Junior High School (414), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Santa Ana Redevelopment (Downtown) (416), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Santa Ana Downtown (416), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - San Luis Obispo General Plan (418), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - San Fernando Valley Child Guidance Clinic (428), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Managua, Nicaragua Part 1 (429), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Managua, Nicaragua Part 2 (429), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Managua, Nicaragua Part 3 (429), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - United States post Office Airport Station (434), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Long Beach Housing (435), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Cancun (441), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Golf de Vallarta Land Analysis (445), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - San Bernardino (453), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - New York Tracon (FAA) (461), 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - UCSD Third College Phase 2 (462), 1976 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Mission College Feasibility Study (467), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Los Tules (470), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Wilshire Corridor (475), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Southern California Rapid Transit District (SCRTD) Wilshire Corridor (475), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Dana Environmental (477), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Huntington Beach Condominium (478), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Condessa Vallarta (488), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Dana Point Design Development (Model) (501), 1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Van Nuys State Office Building (507), 1979 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - UCLA Memorial Activities Center Building D (524), 1979 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Fort MacArthur Comprehensive Plan (523), 1979 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Maguire Community Redevelopment Agency (CRA) Bunker Hill (526), 1980 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Carson Community Hall (527), 1980 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Drew School (534), 1980 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Drew School Medical Education (535), 1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Fort MacArthur Housing (543), 1980 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Long Beach Transit (546), 1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Social Biology Building (547), 1980 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Parkview Plaza (550), 1981 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - LAX Parking Structure 3 and 4 (551), 1981 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Loma Linda VA Facility (558), 1981 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - One La Brea Place (569), 1982 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Union Station Baggage Handling (574), 1983 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - UCLA School of Engineering (582), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - UCLA Boelter Hall Retrofit (582), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Missile Crew Training Facility (1984) (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Washington Gym (586.3), 1985 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Long Beach Light Rail, Yards and Shops (590), 1985 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - 77th Street Police Station (597), 1986 (Box 55, Folder 15-18)
    - Silverlake Recreation Center (620), 1988 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Jefferson New Senior High School (625), 1988 (Box 55, Folder 20, Box 56, Folder 1)
    - King/Drew Trauma Addition (637), 1989 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - United States Postal Service General Mail Facility, Vehicle Maintenance Facility (USPS) (GMF/VMF) (651), 1990 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Fame 24000 Western Avenue (655), 1990 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Allen House Parking (Fame) (655/655.2), 1990 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - California State University Los Angeles Science Labs (656), 1990 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Lynwood Service Center (669), 1985 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - California State University Los Angeles University Club (685), 1985 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Hollywood Bowl (689), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Baldwin Hills Recreation Center (690), 1994 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Drew University - New Master Plan (706), 1995 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Kulka's Residence (74), 1959 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - California Museum of Science & Industry Peer Review, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - LA County Metropolitan Transportation Authority Transit- Based Housing Symposium Outline & Agenda, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Charles R. Drew Post-Graduate Medical School Campus Master Plan, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook School District (119), undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Sommers' Residence, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Hidden Trails Lodge (105), 1959 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Telecomputer Corporation (124), 1961 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Martin Luther King / Drew Medical Center Transparencies (637), 1989 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Microfilm, 1960s-1980s (Box 64, Box 65, Box 66)
      Box 64 contains 6 reels: Temple Emanuel; Emergency Operation Center (463); UCLA Memorial Activities Center (524); UCSD (462); Liberty Square Parking Garage (610); Poway (618).
      Box 65 contains 5 reels: Hyde Park School (258); Dance remodeling; UCSD academic unit 1 (379); Veterans Administration 60 Bed Nursing Home (558) (2 reels).
      Box 66 contains 17 reels: St. Mark's Lutheran Church (316); Hunter's Point Child Care Center Site I (304) (2 reels); Harbor Dental (333); Temple Beth David (306); Central City Community Mental Health Center (270); Carson City Hall North Wing (528); Northwest Recreation Center (405); Crenshaw Probation (338); San Fernando Valley Child Guidance Clinic (364); St. John's Lutheran Church (324); UCLA Kerckhoff Hall (476); ERC Building (503); Oak Center Towers (358); Placentia, Main Post Office (367); Golden State Mutual (406); UCLA Campus Storehouse (439).
    - Negatives, 1962-1978 (Box 61)
      This box contains negatives of drawings attached to cards for the following projects:
      Temple Akiba (188); Los Angeles High School (LAUSD) (362); Third College (379); Carson City Hall (384); Bank of America (454); UCSD Third College Phase 2 (462); Carson Computer Facility (463); Carson North Basement (471); ERC (503).
    - Plans - negatives, Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Series 3: Architectural plans and drawings, 1959-1995
  Conditions Governing Access
  Unprocessed series. This material is unavailable for access. Please see LSC's Access to Unprocessed Collections Policy for more information about levels of discovery and access of special collections materials and registering interest in unprocessed collections.
  This series contains 125 sets of rolled architectural drawings for KDG projects, and 7 boxes of drawings for Kennard's personal residence.
  Other Finding Aids
  A digital copy of the architectural drawings inventory is available via this link: Link to Kennard architectural drawings inventory
- Series 4: Increasing diversity in architecture, 1976-1994
  This series comprises documents that outline Robert Kennard's commitment to increasing diversity in the field of architecture. It includes membership lists to organizations like the NAACP and the National Organization of Minority Architects.
  - Black History Exhibit 1978 U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - African Union of Architects Congress and Special General Assembly, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Compton Executive Interns Program, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cal Poly (Pomona and SLO) Minority Support Program, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Diversity in Architecture Class, Ball State University, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - American Institute of Architects (AIA) College of Fellows Task Force on African Americans into the Profession, Draft Report, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - AIA Architectural Biography Submission - Robert Kennard, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - AIA Different Urban Agenda, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National Institute for Architectural Education, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)